<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="_includes/faqs.xsl"?>

<faqs>

  <faq>
    <q>
		Can I come to the Silver course if I have not attended the Bronze course?
    </q>
    <a>
		Yes you can, if your dog is at the relevant obedience level.
    </a>
  </faq>

  <faq>
    <q>
		Do we have to book into the Silver obedience course?
    </q>
    <a>
		Yes you do have to book into the Silver obedience course, as this is a course that runs for six consecutive weeks.
    </a>
  </faq>

  <faq>
    <q>
		Can children come to the obedience courses?
    </q>
    <a>
		Because the people in the obedience courses are constantly on the move and changing direction, children have to sit on the side and watch. Many do, and they are welcome
    </a>
  </faq>

   <faq>
    <q>
		Do we have to pay in advance when we book into the obedience course?
    </q>
    <a>
	
    </a>
  </faq>

   <faq>
    <q>
		Does my dog need to have had kennel cough vaccination to come to classes? 
    </q>
    <a>
		No your dog does not need to have kennel cough vaccination to come to training classes, but their  yearly  vaccinations need to be up to date.
    </a>
  </faq>

   <faq>
    <q>
		Where are the courses held?
    </q>
    <a>
		They are held at A1K9 Behaviour and Training Academy just outside Pontardulais. (See directions on website) 
    </a>
  </faq>

   <faq>
    <q>
		What do I need to bring with me?
    </q>
    <a>
		Collar, lead and some treats that your dogs like to eat. A  Bring whatever you have and I will advise you what is best to use with your dog.
    </a>
  </faq>

   <faq>
    <q>
		What should I wear?
    </q>
    <a>
		You should wear warm clothes and sturdy shoes as we will work outdoors whenever possible.
    </a>
  </faq>
  
  <faq>
    <q>
		If I miss a week in the Silver course can I have that credited on the next course?
    </q>
    <a>
	
    </a>
  </faq>
  
  <faq>
    <q>
		If it is raining will the class be cancelled?
    </q>
    <a>
		No it will be held indoors, in the training barn.
    </a>
  </faq>
  
</faqs>